# Hyungrok Kim

https://rokrokss.com

: https://github.com/q0115643

**t**: +821089595643

**e**: hyungrok.kim@kaist.ac.kr

## **PROFILE**

Unexperienced but passionated student developer anticipating for the first job to open my career. Belonged in Industrial Design department for 2 years, moved to Computer Science 2 years ago. Studied Data Science and NLP trying to understand the linguistic communication of emotions. Believes firmly that I will relish working as a web developer and serve people with better lives.

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### PLAYSOLUTION (http://povi.co.kr/)

Intern, Frontend Developer

Design and Develop Web Dashboard used tomanage exchanges between content-providers, store-owners, distributers.

Angular2, Typescript

Jul 2017 - Aug 2017 Dajeon, Republic of Korea

UILAB(http://uilab.kr/) **Undergraduate Researcher** 

Study on Metaphor Comperhension

Jul 2018 - Dec 2018 Dajeon, Republic of Korea

## **ORGANIZATION**

#### Korea Design Membership(http://kidp.or.kr)

Attend various design classes

Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology**

B.S. in Computer Science Minor in Industrial Design

Mar 2014 - Present Daejeon, Korea

## **CORSEWORKS**

#### **CS Major**

CS574 Natural Language Processing CS570 Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning CS492 Introduction to Machine Learning CS474 Text Mining CS470 Introduction to Artificial Intelligence CS330 Operating Systems and Lab CS320 Programming Language **CS311 Computer Organization** CS300 Introduction to Algorithms CS230 System Programming CS206 Data Structure

#### Others

ID307 Interface Design **ID220 Interaction Prototyping** ID302 Space Design **ID301 Product Design Factors** ID219 Computer-Aided Design ID214 Digital Design Graphics **ID213 Product Design Fundamentals** ID212 Three-Dimensional Design ID217 Presentation Technique **ID218 Photo Techniques** ID215 Introduction to Industrial Design MAS109 Introduction to Linear Algebra MAS205 Probability and Statistics

## **PROJECTS**

#### **ROKUROKU**

https://rokuroku.work/

Build web to show japanese old short-comics to viewers but mainly for my personal web development practice.

Django, React, Create-React-App, JavaScript, Sass, Nginx, uWSGI, Docker Mar 2019 - Dec 2019

#### **Neural Poetry Scansion**

CS204 Discrete Mathematics



Based on Original Paper(Proceedings of AAAI 2016), deep-learning apporach to improve performance on poety-analysis

Pytorch, BiLSTM-CRF, Word2Vec May 2018 - Aug 2018

#### **Arithmetic Hash**

Build LSTM-based query encoder designed to replace the hash algorithm of p2p network

Pytorch, RNN, Markov Model Jan 2019

#### HarmonyTable



Hardware project of combining harmony & turntable in Interaction Prototyping

Arduino

Sep 2016 - Oct 2016

#### **GCN-RNNG** based Korean NMT



Syntax-Aware Model for Neural Machine Translation with Morpheme Structure in Korean

Pytorch, SyntaxNet, GCN, RNNG, KoNLPy, Word2Vec May 2018 - Aug 2018

#### **Rich Context Competition**

https://coleridgeinitiative.org/richcontextcompetition





Deep Learning based model to comprehend scientific researches extract research fields, methods, and dataset usages

Pytorch, ELMo, BiLSTM-CRF, Word2Vec

Nov 2018 - Dec 2018

#### **FlyDuck**



Processing, Arduino Nov 2016 - Dec 2016



#### Logo Design for Aging.kaist.ac.kr



Their name used to be "WATCH", the lab with a focus on aging, social welfare, and technology policy at KAIST

Feb 2016